本片由‘新气息论坛’‘001影视网’联合出品
最新电影首发，万部电影，电视剧下载
新气息论坛www.xinqixi.com 001影视网www.001ys.com
字幕翻译-航空母舰
校正-新气息论坛字幕组
利物浦 1760年
Liverpool 1760
人们常说：血浓于水
It is said that blood is thicker than water
血在定义我们，约束我们
It is what defined us, bind us
诅咒我们
curses us
来吧，巴纳巴斯
Come on, Barnabas
对一些人来说，探究生命的意义远超过财富和权力
For some learn the mean the life over wealth and privilege
而对其他人来说，这反而只是一种孤独的生活方式
for others a life of solitude
安琪莉科，我告诉你多少次，不要盯着他看
Angelique, how many times do. I tell you not to stare at him
记住你的身份！
Remember your place
当我还是个小男孩的时候
When I was but a boy
父亲带我们来到一个新的世界
My father took us to the new world
去扩大柯林斯家族帝国
To expand the Collins family empire
我们把英国工业发展到了荒芜的缅因州
We brought English industry to the wild maine
并在那经营起了美国还未接触过的捕鱼业
and build a fishing business the like of which America had never seen
一年之后
One year later
一个人应该为他所建立的感到自豪
A man should take pride in what he builds
但是记住，巴纳巴斯
But remember, Barnabas
家庭才是唯一真正的财富
Family is the only real wealth
随着我们事业的发展
As our business grew
柯林斯港口小镇也繁荣起来
The town of Collins Port grew with it
于是我们决定在这扎根
and we decided to put down permanent roots
之后，我们在接下来的15年里不断建设我们心爱的家园
We spent the next 15 years building our beloved home
柯林斯伍德庄园
Collins Wood
但不是每个人都可以分享我们家族的成功
But not everyone share in our family success
爱我吧
love
告诉我说“安格莉科，我爱你，我需要你”
Let me hear you say I love you, Angelique and I want you
安格莉科，抱歉。但是……
Angelique, I am sorry my dear, but..
你这是在让我撒谎
you would be hearing a lie
（咒语）强大起来吧
make the high and mighty
蔑视一切生灵，使他们都臣服于你
Arrogant creatures down you go
这让我的父母在毫无预兆的意外中死去
The links to my parents were no accident
我开始沉迷于黑暗魔法和远古咒语
I became obsessed with dark magic and ancient curses
（咒语）在地狱大门之前注视着
behold upon the gates of hell
如果我独自看到字符
If I saw the characters alone
那将是撒旦的真实名字，我会在此祈祷
Blessed upon the satan true name
（撒旦的真实名字）
Myvestvuolas
但在那时，即使我的悲伤逆流成河
But even then in my depth of my grief
黑暗也不是我生命里的全部，我觅到了真爱
not all was darkness,I have found my one true love
你发誓我们会永远在一起
promise me we'd be together forever
好。我以上帝之名发誓，乔赛特。我发誓
God is my witness Josette.I swear it
所有的女仆人都几乎和我有染
Of all the servants I could have sperm
她们的心我可以随意伤害
all the hearts that I could have broken
我有了一个秘密
I got the one secret
我和一个女巫有了关系
I got the Witch
（施咒）如果他有了新欢，且是真爱，爱让他柔情似水
if he dug another true love to relent his heart
那么，我和我的魔法将会把他定格在年轻时期
让他看着他所爱之人
And I and Magic shall dis-might his youth so all he loves will
死去
die
因为被卷入安格莉科的咒语 我心爱的乔赛特
Caught in Angelique spells My beloved Josette
被魔法驱使，无能为力的来到海边的悬崖
wanders helplessly to those hill
在那里，许多丧失希望的灵魂曾经坠入死亡地狱
where many of the despondent soul have leap to their death
乔赛特！
Josette
救我
Help me
乔赛特！
Josette
你都做了些什么？
What have you done?
安吉丽科诅咒我，让我变成了一个吸血鬼
Angelique had curse me to be a vampire
这样我的痛苦会永无止境的（这里指失去爱人之痛）
so that my suffering would never ends
他是魔鬼！
There is the monster
自此，我和乔赛特生死两隔
Result that I would never belong to her
安格丽科蛊惑镇民让他们敌视我
Angelique turn the towns people against me
我被困住让我孤独忍受着悲痛，沉浸在无尽的黑暗之中
And condemned me to suffer my anguish alone in the dark
漫无天日
for all time
让我出去！
Let me out I say
放开我
Release me
招聘家庭教师
GOVERNESS WANTED
你好，我是麦琪伊……
Hello, My name is Maggie Yves
你好，我是维多利亚温特
Hello, my name is Victoria Winters
请叫我维姬
Please call me Vicky
你从哪里来，维罗妮卡？
So where are you from you, Veronica?
纽约，我的名字是维多利亚
New York, and it's Victoria
维多利亚。哈，我喜欢这个小妞
and it's Victoria, I love this chick man
一次纽约旅行？ - 大概是吧
- New York's a trip huh? - I guess
那你呢？
What about you?,
为了什么让你从纽约大城市来到州县？
What bring New York girl up to the states?
一个故友
An old friend
玩的愉快，维罗妮卡
Take it easy, Veronica
-你好，我是维多利亚温特 -恭喜你啊
- Hello, I'm Victoria Winters - Congratulations
我到这里是要来看看是否有家庭女教师的职位
I'm here to see about the governess position
很好，我一直在等你
Well I'm been expecting you
进来吧
Come on
抱歉没去车站接你。该死的马车毛病不断
Sorry I didn't pick you up at the station damn wagon been acting up
伊丽莎白花了很多的钱修这个地方
Elizabeth most spend getting the place fix
好漂亮
It's beautiful
嗯，不过有很多灰尘
Full with dust is all it has
这个地方大的应该有一百名侍从才对
Place was designed for staff of a hundred
现在却只有我和约翰逊女士
And now the only staff is me Me and Mrs Johnson
而她，现在老到已经像没有底的桶，没有用了
She but as useful as a bucket without a bottom
并不是每一个家庭都有像这样子的房子
Still not every family has a house like this
用一个城镇的名字来命名它！
or a whole town name of them
- 什么？ - 柯林斯，柯林斯港口
- Come again? - Collins, Collins Port
我忘记了
I forgot that
他是谁？
Who's that?
可能是巴纳比吧，名字里有Barn
（barn有谷仓的意思，前面四个字母,暗指很有钱）
Barnaby maybe,Some part of Barn
大概是个很重要的人物
Must be the important one from way back
这要追溯到他们还是很富有的人的时候
Back they were rich-rich people
巴纳巴斯
Barnabas
他的名字是巴纳巴斯 柯林斯
His name was Barnabas Collins
他是这个家族里最优秀的人
and he's the finest man this family had ever knew
欢迎来到柯林斯伍德庄园
Welcome to collins Wood
你会在这里很愉快
you have to imagine us on a better day
这个房子里有200个房间，大部分都关闭了
The house has some 200 rooms most closed off
为了节省暖气
to save on heating
我们甚至都不去那些老侧厅了
We don't even go in the old wing anymore
请坐
Sit
这里总共有七个人
There are only 7 of us after all
我的女儿， 卡罗琳和 我
My daughter, Caroline and I
我的哥哥罗杰 和 他的儿子，戴维
My brother Roger and his son, David
还有你刚才见到的
Willy who you met
约翰逊女士和霍夫曼医生
Mrs. Johnson and Dr. Hoffman
我猜约翰逊女士整日昏睡和她具有传奇特色的宿醉有关
Who I suspect is sleeping off on her legendary hangovers
如果你不介意我想问一下 戴维的妈妈在哪里？
And where is David's mother? If you don't mind my asking
劳拉在海上失踪了
Laura was lost at sea
那时候大戴维才五岁
When David was 5
他经历了一段很痛苦的时期才接受了她的死亡
He had a rather difficult time accepting her passing
我把霍夫曼医生带来，和他一起工作过一个月
I brought the Doctor Hoffman here to work with him for a month
那是三年之前的事情了
That was 3 years ago
我也有些问题要问如果你不介意的话
I have just a few questions if you don't mind
-这不是例行行规和程序化询问 - 当然
- That were not on the application  - Of course
你觉得总统（这里指的是尼克松）怎么样？
How do you feel about the president?
从来没见过
Never met him
战争？（小译认为应该是指美国水门事件）-我没有看电视
- The war? - I don't watch Television
你觉得男女应该平等吗？
Do you think the sexes should be equal?
上帝也不希望吧
Heavens no
这将让人类变得不好管理
Men would become unmanageable
我认为我们会相处得很愉快，温特小姐
I I we'll get along just fine Miss Winters
维姬，叫我维姬就行
Vicky, please.Call me Vicky
卡罗琳
Caroline
卡罗琳，这是温特小姐
Caroline, this is Miss Winters
你是纽约来的？-是
- Miss New York - I am
曼哈顿怎么样？
What Manhattan like?
我16岁的时候将去那里生活
I'm going to live there when I'm 16
卡罗琳非常迷恋 我也同意了
Caroline has a fantasy that I going allow this
如果她不同意，我会自己偷着去
and mother has a fantasy that I wouldn't run away if she doesn't
那么你是来做保姆且监督我的？
So you're here to babysit the lunny?
告诉你多少遍，不要用那个单词
What have I told you about using that word
- 我来是教戴维的。- 嗯，希望你好运。
- I'm here to teach David - Good luck
没有几个老师可以坚持超过一周
Most of the others last only a week
- 温特小姐 - 请叫我维姬。
- Miss Winters - Please, call me Vicky
快切牛排（仆人名字），我饿了
Chop chop Jullianne, I'm starving
上帝保佑我这个骨髓干流行男士（指自己很瘦）
God help me if it another Bone Dry Pop Roasta
这位是？
Who's this?
温特小姐，这是我的哥哥，罗杰
Miss Winters, this is my brother, Roger
罗杰，温特小姐将是戴维的新任家庭教师
Roger Miss Winters is to be David new governess
请叫我维姬
Please, call me Vicky
- 很高兴见到你 - 恩恩
- Nice to meet you - Yeah, yeah
也很高兴见到你
Nice to meet you
你在撒谎
You're a liar
我能透过你的脸知道你想什么
I can tell you know just by a person's face
你的脸告诉我
Yours says
我看起来甜美安静但是我藏着秘密
I might look sweet and innocent,but I hide secrets
一个让我毛发会竖起的秘密
Secrets that make my hairs stand up
离她远些，朱莉娅
Leave her be Julia
你是医生
You're the doctor
是，你是保姆 因为她是个不错的的人（暗讽反话）
Yeah and you're the nanny,because she's a catch
你觉得会和我们相处融洽吗
How do you ever expect to live with us if
如果你在做介绍的时候贴标签
you keep introducing each other with labels
那么维琪
So Vicky
卡罗琳，你能把那噪音关上吗？
Caroline, would you please turn that noise down
戴维，这是维琪 她将是你新的家庭教师
David this is Vicky,she's going to be your new governess
全被你毁了，我本来想吓吓她
You ruin it, I was going to scare her
妈的，戴维，我不是告诉过你在你的床单上弄上洞吗
Damn it David, what did I told you about putting holes into the sheet?
它们是埃及棉（这里父亲怕他呼吸不畅）
Those were Egyptian cotton
我想吓吓她，你害怕了吗
I was going to scare her,Are you scared?
吓坏了
Terrified beyond belief
你不用迁就他  因为他就一傻子
You don't have to be nice because he's nuts you know
卡罗琳
Caroline
卡罗琳经常摸她自己然后发出像猫叫的声音
（这里指她自慰，你懂的）
Caroline touches herself and make noises like a kitten
- 戴维 ―他在撒谎，去死
- David - He's lying, shit
卡罗琳，够了。你们两个
Caroline, enough. Both of you
我介意问么，这个家庭经营什么？
If I may, what is the family business?
海鲜，温特小姐
Seafood. Miss Winters
我们在镇上有个大的罐口食品厂
We have a large cannery in town
我们还有些捕鱼船
We still own a few fishing boats
但他们都沉底在海洋里,戴维的妈妈在其中一艘的底部
and David's mother at the bottom of one of them
卡罗琳，去你的房间
Caroline, go to your room
在这房间的每个人都为自己着想不会顾及我的感受
Everybody in this house take his side and never care what I feel
她没有死
She didn't die
-她不会死 - 够了，戴维
- She can't  - Enough David
是，戴维一直深信她的妈妈永生
Yes, David really believe his mother some kind of being immortality
这个很刺激
fascinating really
我感觉到她
I feel her
她和我说话，一直都是
She talk to me, all the time
好吧
Well
我认为鬼魂他们
I think ghost are just people who moved
在一个和人类不同的维度存在着
to a slightly different dimension than ours
而且我觉得有些人类有能力看到他们
and I think some people have antenna strong enough to pick them up
这是有科学依据支持的……
There's actually scientific evidence to support...
谢谢你温特小姐
Thank you Miss Winters
戴维你吓到我了
David you startled me
开始准备万圣节了吗
Getting ready for Halloween?
他来了
He's coming
我们碰到东西了，快挖出来
We hit something, lets dig it out
-他妈的到底是什么？-不会是输气管道吧
- What the hell is this? - You think its a gas main?
应该是，别期望是别的什么东西
Not suppose to be any out here
别哄我了，快拿些断线钳来
You got to be shitting me.Grab me some bolt cutters
上帝啊
Jesus
快跑
Run
我很抱歉
I am terribly sorry
你们想不到我多么渴
You can't even imagine how thirsty I am
撒旦
Myvestvuolas
让我看看你，撒旦
Show yourself, Satan
别用你奇怪的发光来嘲笑我
Mock me not with your strange luminescent
好奇怪
Curiously strange
这是什么
What is this?
一些幽灵
Some specter approaches
是恶魔的眼睛已经看到我了
Is it the eyes of the devil himself to drag me to my judgment?
靠近我，魔王.我的灵魂已经为你准备好了
Approached me, Lucifer My soul is prepared
傻帽
Assholes
我心爱的柯林斯伍德庄园
My beloved collins Wood
他们对你做了什么？
What have they done to you?
不要喝威士忌，我又不是只狗
Not drink whiskey and I'm not a dog
我要一直喝啊
I will keep on drinking
嗨，南瓜
Hi pumpkin
你估计因为怕我就不醉了
Fear me not drunker
让你告诉我我想知道的应该不是很难
You shall not be harm as long as you tell me all that I need to know
这就是你想知道的全部
That's all you need to know
看着我
See me
看着我的眼睛
Look into my eyes
把你内心深处的想法传给我
and deliver me your inner most thought
醒过来
Awaken
很好
Well done
现在告诉我关于柯林家族的一切
Now tell me the Collin's family
- 他们居然活下来繁衍了后代 - 他们，他们中的四个
- Do they endure     - They are, four of them
谢天谢地
Thanks heaven
- 现在几月了? - 十月
- What month is it? - October
- 所以有南瓜 - 什么年份
- Thatˇs why there is pumpkin - What is the year?
1972年，是的
1972,Yeah, 1972
1972?
听我说 未来的居住者
Hear me future dweller
你将会是我忠实的仆人直到
you shall be my loyal servant until such time
我释放了你
as I release you
- 你第一个主人是谁？- 你必须净化我
- So, what first master? - You must cleanse me
然后你带我到你所提到的柯林斯庄园
then you will take me to these living collins whom you speak of
好吧
Okay
你见过这样的威严？
Have you ever seen such majesty?
谁能够设想欧洲的这份荣耀
How is it a person manage European allegiance
和美国人的企业
and American Enterprise
在这个世界上最好的九个手工设计师知道
nine of the finest craftsmen in the world will ever know
巧夺天工，无与伦比
and life the closes of carving glorious masterpiece
他们为艺术献出心血
And they all contribute blood sacrifice arts for you
你看这吊灯的错综复杂精致程度
the complexity of this magnificent chandelier
这只有在贵族皇宫里才可以见到
can only be found in the palace of nobility
壁炉
The fireplace
大部分都是采用质量上乘的大理石雕刻而成
Sculptured entirely of most exquisite of marbles
大理石来自意大利福罗伦达州这座城市
from city, Florence, Italy
非常牢固结实
and joined creating more power
你被麻醉了吗？
Are you stoned or something?
亲爱的，他们的确是想把我迷醉，但是这是徒然的
They try stoning me my dear, and did not worked
他们什么时候允许女人在晚上出来了，仆人？
When did they start allowing woman on the night on this day, servant?
卡罗琳
Caroline
- 看 - 额，是
- Look  - Ah yes
不可思议是吗？
Uncanny is it not?
值得我花时间去构想摆姿势
Worth every hour I spent posing
抱歉，我的名字是巴纳巴斯柯林斯
Forgive me, my name is Barnabas Collins
我是 戴维 柯林斯
I'm David Collins
- 我们是？- 亲戚？大概你这么认为
- Are we? - Relatived?, distantly you might say
很高兴认识你，戴维
It was a pleasure to make your acquaintance master David
孩子们
Children
远离那个男人
Get away from that man
他说他是巴纳巴斯柯林斯
He says his name was Barnabas Collins
而且我很确定他觉得我是个妓女
and I'm pretty sure he called me a hooker
这样子就行了，卡罗琳
That will do Caroline
我想跟你谈谈
A word, please
如果这是个玩笑，请考虑一下演奏方式
If this is some kind of a joke,considered it played
如果你是为了继承钱来的，我恐怕你信息很不足
If its money you're after,I'm afraid you been misinformed
但是无论你是谁，你不准再招惹这些孩子
But who ever you are, you are to not look at those children again
我说清楚了吗？
Am I clear?
夫人，你把话题转到家庭
Your diversion to family
是可以允许的
is admirable madam
而且你的怀疑
and your suspicions
我也可以理解
understandable
一个陌生的访问者声称自己是你的远房亲属
A stranger arrive, claiming to be a distance relation
问题是你想到的动机很对
question of motive is to be expected
作为科林斯家族一员
As a Collins
看来你已经意识到了我们家族曾经历了一段很长时间的黑暗期
surely you are aware of the darkness that have long played in our family
你是指诅咒？
You mean our curse?
关乎鬼魂和吸血鬼的
Which is ghosts and vampires
神话
Myths
这些大概都发生在你之前很多年吧
and like so many before you
自然我觉得你大概是用它们来谋取钱财
I suppose you are to get rid of them for a price of course
我能证明我（跟那些骗子）的不同处
I can prove as I am different
首先，我不是为了钱才以此证明
Firstly, I do not come seeking money rather to provide it
其次
Secondly,
我像了解我自己一样了解这座房子里面的
I know the of this mansion as well as my own
的每一个隐蔽处，每一个角落
Every nook, every corner
每一个秘密
Every secret
它们都保存着我的东西
There's where I keep my things
真是可耻的滥用啊
A disgraceful misuse
印象深刻
Impressive
但是老房子里面都大部分隐藏暗门
but there are plenty of old houses with hidden doors
我希望你有其三
I hope you have a Thirdly
事实上，告诉我
Indeed, tell me
你都知道些什么
What do you know
-关于巴纳巴斯柯林斯 - 他是个传奇人物
-of Barnabas Collins - Just legends really
他很自信，强壮
He was confident and strong
受人尊重
Admires by all
但是他觉得他父母的死亡跟家族受到诅咒
but he believe our family was cursed and
有关系之后，他就疯了
when his parents were killed, he went mad
始终坚持沉迷下去，最终被女巫变成了一个吸血鬼
went around insisting that witch had turned him into a vampire
你关于他的死知道些什么
What is known of his death?
傻帽都不知道
Nothing
-这个我无从知道- 那就对了，夫人
-Not that I can think of  - Thatˇs madam
因为他根本不会死
is because he never died
我就是巴纳巴斯柯林斯
I am Barnabas Collins
-那意味着你是……-吸血鬼，夫人
- That means your - A vampire, Madam
是的
Yes
非常痛恨
and most regrettably so
但是很重要的是我是科林斯家园的人
but more importantly I am a Collins
我将给予你承诺
And I give you a word of honor
不只是你，这个房子里所有的人都不用担心
rather you or many or any under this roof need fear
我的诅咒
my cursed nature
我父亲在这个房间里设置了很多的密室
My father had a quite of flare of secret passages and rooms
小时候
as a boy
我就兴冲冲的去发掘每一个密室
I took it upon myself to discover each one
这个密室是我最喜欢的
but this one, this one was always my favourite
家庭是这个世界上最真实的财富
Family is the only real wealth that worth a lot
即使他说得很清楚
though clearly
但他却没有反对另一种
he did not oppose to other kind
天哪
Oh my God
我们竟然这些年一直住在一个宝藏室的上面
We been sitting on top of a fortune all these years
知道这个
know this
我的意思是说
I mean to stay
我也是这个家庭的一份子这也将重新是家庭的一部分
I mean to be a part of this family again
-不过有个条件  -说
- On one condition  - Yes
对我承诺
Promise me that this
这些将是我们之间的秘密
All of this will remain our secret
好
So be it
伙伴
Partners
欢迎回到巴纳巴斯家园
Welcome home Barnabas Collins
我被有着铁牙的龙给弄醒了
I was awaken by yellow dragon with iron teeth
面对着大大小小发光的数千盏花灯
confronted by giant little luminescent of a thousand lanterns
他将一直和我们一起住下去吗
He just stay with us forever is he?
我喜欢他
I like him
是啊，我觉得什么事情在英国都不一样吧
Yes, I'm sure things are different in England
那么，巴纳巴斯，你家是经营什么产业
So, Barnabas, what sort of business you in back home?
柯林斯家族有着强大的产业
The Collins family has always been efficient business
但是两个世纪后，我已经决定
but after two centuries of considerations, I have decided
我将将全部心血花在
to devote my entire eternity to
-家庭上 -他意思是看起来像两个世纪过去了
-family - He mean it seem like 2 centuries
早上好
Good Morning
你是谁
Who the hell is this?
霍夫曼医生，这是我们的远房亲戚
Dr. Hoffman, this is our distance relative
巴纳巴斯柯林斯，巴纳巴斯家族第三代
Barnabas Collins, the third
传人，这个来自英国的巴纳巴斯家族成员将给我们一起住
Barnabas Collins, the third is going to stay with us from England
巴纳巴斯
Barnabas
朱莉霍夫曼医生
Doctor Julia Hoffman
天哪
My God
竟然是一个女的医生
A woman doctor
这个世道怎么了
What an age this is
他是认真的吗？
Is he for real?
他仅仅是因为长途劳顿导致太过疲惫
He's just tired from his long trip
我看你已经费尽心机让这些家族银器发出光来
I see you have grown desperate enough to give off the family silverware
你怎么能说这些都是复制品
How can you tell, these are the exact replicas
如果这些是真正的银，我的手
Had this fork being real silver, my hand would
只要轻轻一碰就会燃烧起来
have burst into flame upon the slightest touch
对了，你说过，你有个糟糕的金属过敏症
Yes, you mentioned, you have a terrible metal allergies
无论如何，渔业生意都没有了
anyway, the fishing business had all but gone
那些传统都要快消失了
the manner is nearly in ruins
我就已经回来了，同时你们也会尽快的
Well I have returned and in short order
重振我们的财富
so shall our fortune
祝你好运，安琪已经在缅因州拥有大量的船
Good luck, Angie had deal with most of the boats in Maine
-安琪？ -安琪海湾？
- Angie - Angel Bay
他们已经拥有了东海岸的各个港口
They taken just about every port in east coast
托你的福，我就是要从这里开始我的工作
That is where my work begins with your blessing
我会使我家事业恢复昔日的辉煌
I shall restore the family business to its former glory
乔塞特
Josette
她是维琪，她和我一样相信鬼魂的存在
That's Vicky, she believe in ghost like me
你好
Hi
我非常着迷
I enchanted
你为什么不让他们叫你维琪
surely you don't let them call you Vicky
像维多利亚的名字是多么好听
A name like Victoria is so beautiful
我已经不能分辨出他们的每一个美妙的单音了
I could not bare to part any single syllable of it
嗨，对了
Yeah, well
也许在你来的地方钱可以在树上生长 （钱可生钱）
Money might grow money on trees where you're from
但是我们这里很少见
but it's a little to come by here
不用担心我的能力
Do not concern yourself with my methods
我想立即看到工厂
I shall like to see the factory immediately
马匹多久能准备好？
How soon can the horses be ready?
我们没有马
We don't have horses
我们有雪佛兰汽车
We have a Chevrolet
你好，安琪莉科，祝你愉快
Hi Angelique, have a nice day
-早上好  -安琪
- Good morning  - Angie
早上好
Good Morning
原创翻译首发，更多最新电影下载，电视剧下载
新气息论坛www.xinqixi.com 001影视网www.001ys.com
一个设备坏了
One of the equipment blew
要等2个小时才能再放回生产线
going to be two hours before its back online
只能一个小时
Make it an hour
这里停止对接几个小时了
stop docking hours in here,
今天每个人看起来怎么都慢了半拍
everybody looks like they're moving at half speed today
老实说，我觉得他们
To tell you the truth I think they're just
可能被昨晚发生的事情有点吓到了
a little spook about what happen last night
-你是什么意思？ -难道你没有听说吗？
- What do you mean? - Didn't you hear?
今天早上他们发现11个工人死在森林里的9号公路
They found 11 workers dead in the wood off route 9 this morning
- 好啦,发生事故了？ -那不是事故
- Well accidents happens - It wasn't an accident
一些疯子撕破了他们的喉咙
Some maniac rip their throats out
9号线在哪里？
Where off route 9?
好拉，已经敲了20遍了
Alright, I heard you the first 20 times
穿好你那该死的裤子等我开门
Keep your damn panties
-在 -我会尽力做的最好
- on   - I'll do my best
请叫一个巴纳巴斯 科林斯的人
A word with Barnabas Collins  please
哦，他是（嗯），谁？
Oh he's um, who?
我认为你会知道呀是谁的
I think you know who
黑色的头发，英俊的相貌
black hair, handsome features,
沾着新鲜血液的奇怪衣服
strange clothes,covered in fresh blood
哇。我们让这个地方去地狱吧，怎么样？
My, we let this place go to hell haven't we?
也许那里才是属于它的地方
Right, it belongs to that
你一定是卡罗琳
you must be Caroline
是你属于充满深情的生物
You belonging to quite affectionate creature
-安琪莉科 -伊丽莎白
- Angelique  - Elizabeth
你看起来气色很好
You're looking well
那么，你我将会共享快乐吗
And to what do we owe the pleasure?
我在这里代表镇议会
I'm here on behalf of the Town Council
欢迎我们的新访客来到柯林斯港
Welcoming our new visitor to Collins Port
-我想他应该睡着了 -在白天？
- He's asleep I'm afraid  - During the day?
-真奇怪， 那是什么恶魔的砰砰声
- How odd   - What was that infernal banging
-巴纳巴斯，我们有一个客人 -我的失礼，夫人
- Barnabas, we have a guests - My apologies Madam
我刚起床
I have just risen
-你不要怕，女士 -你好，巴纳巴斯
- You mustn't be frightened, Miss..- Hello Barnabas
我叫安琪 布沙尔
My name is Angie Bouchard
嗯 的确
So it is
你知道我是多么的想你
You know what I would very much like to do with you?
我只能想象
I can only imagine
我真的很想再和你私下说说话
I would really much like a word in the drawing room
如果你允许，伊丽莎白，你会原谅我们吗？
With your permission Elizabeth 。Would you excuse us?
你怎么敢用我卑劣的手段对我？
How dared you defy my manner with obnoxious
真正的你
Its really you
你怎么敢用你的邪恶的嘴唇亲吻我
How dared you place your wicked lips upon me
我记得这个地方过去不那么令人沮丧
I remember this place being less depressing
还记得这工具带来很大乐趣
And also remember the tools having a lot of fun
这里
here
还有
and
这里
here
你知道你让我受尽折磨吗？
Have you any idea what you put me through?
你杀光了我爱的人，还把我诅咒变成了可怕的生物
You killed all my lover and curse to be this hideous creature
巴纳巴斯 忘记那些事吧
Barnabas get over it
200年来，我一直苟活在棺木里
I lived in a box for 200 years
不要夸大事实 只有196年
Don't exaggerate its only a 196
课我就像度过了永恒一样
It was an eternity
我真的应该拿你来试验一下魔法，把你烤成肉排
I should have you trial for witchcraft and burn to the steak
可怜的巴纳巴斯
Poor sweet Barnabas
当你小睡的时候，所有的东西已经变了
Thing have changed while you were taking your nap
现在的科林斯港口变成了我的天使湾
My Angel Bay is Collins Port now
所以是你把柯林斯家族的产业推向了深渊
So are the one who sent the Collins family business into the abyss
这里他们爱着我
They love me here
山中无老虎猴子称大王
I'm the only big fish left in the pond
真的是这样吗？
Is that so?
只有善良的柯林斯港人知道
only the good people of Collins Port knows
他们心爱的安琪只不过是卑贱的恶魔
that their beloved Angie is a whore of Beelzebub
你真的认为所有人会相信你说的话吗？
Do you really think anyone would believe a word you said?
这个小镇还会有人支持你200年吗？
having enough standing member of this community for 200 years
一个接一个
in one port to another
虽然你的名字改变了，但你仍然是
Your name may have changed but you remained
一个恶魔
a Satan
一个卑贱的恶魔
a devil hooker
现在柯林斯港的人都崇拜信徒了 （信春哥了）
The people of Collins Port admires worshipers now
对他们来说，你只不过是个连阳光都不敢直视的陌生人
and to them you just a stranger whose afraid of the sun
欢迎回到黑暗深渊，巴纳巴斯 柯林斯
Welcome back to the shadow ，Barnabas Collins
我想念你
I miss you
天使湾
Angel Bay
真是一个令人作呕的名字
the only dusty name summons vomits
我一直都知道关于安琪的事，除了她是女巫的事实
I always knew there were something off about Angie, but a witch?
真的
Indeed
一个非常怨恨我的女巫
A witch with an impenetrable hatred of me
怨恨？不是，如果她只是讨厌你，她早就应该杀了你
Hate? No, if she merely hated you,she would've killed you
诅咒是需要祭品的
A curse takes devotion
为什么我必须孤独？
Why must I alone
忍受着这个害群之马？
bear the rotten fruit on our cursed family tree?
我的父母被夺走了
My parents were taken
我的真爱
My true love
夺走了
taken
那你做了什么
and what did you do?
我尝试去跳悬崖
I attempt to throw myself off a cliff
悲催的是我跳了
tragically I did
然后
and then
我变成了一个吸血鬼
I became a vampire
开始杀害无辜的城镇的人们
Started to kill innocent Towns people
没错
Yes
但你也让家族得以延续下去
but you also kept the family afloat
努力使风俗不被瓦解
and try to keep the manner from falling apart
对
Yes
是的，我确实做了，不是吗？  -你一直在战斗，巴纳巴斯
- Yes, I did didn't I?  - You fought on Barnabas
以你自己疯狂而痛苦的方式在战斗着
In your own crazy and miserable way, you fought on
知道他们不得不把你拖走兵锁在一个棺木里
until they had to drag you away and lock you in an iron box
- 为了让你停止反抗 -天哪，你是对的
- to keep you from fighting  - My god, you're right
你在战斗，是因为战斗已经融入了你的血液里
You fought on because it's in you blood,
是我们的血液  夫人
In our blood Madam
现在你有机会再战
and now you had the chance to fight again
我会去战斗
and fight I shall
本片由‘新气息论坛’‘001影视网’原创翻译出品
最新电影首发，万部电影，电视剧下载
新气息论坛www.xinqixi.com 001影视网www.001ys.com
这是什么魔法？
What sorcery this?
显露你的真面目吧，妹子
Reveal yourself tiny songstist
如果你想要渔民，首先你要去找 赛拉斯 柯拉仁
if you want fishermen you got to get Silas Client first
他知道从巴尔港到波士顿的每一个船长
he knew every captain from Bar Harbor to Boston
他们称他为大浅滩教父
They call him the godfather of the Grand Banks
Clarena船长
Captain Clarena
Clarena船长我希望你能见见巴纳巴斯 柯林斯
Captain Clarena I like you to meet Barnabas Collins
柯林斯？
Collins?
柯林斯家人有什么要跟我谈的吗？
and why does Collins want to talk to me?
想要和你签一个合同 - 我有合同了
- To offer you a contract   - I have a contract
和天使湾的
with Angel Bay
如果我告诉你 我可以给你更好的待遇
and if I told you I could offer you a better one
柯林斯先生，我可以告诉你的
Then Mr Collins I would tell you
此恨绵绵无绝期 (永远不可能的意思)
to take a long walk of a short tear
这就是我这一行的忠诚
There are such a thing as loyalty in our line of work
我明白
I see
Clarena先生
Mr Clarena
对于天使湾的工资你已经感到相当疲惫了
You have grown rather weary working for Angel Bay
事实上 你宁愿将你的灵魂出卖给撒旦
In fact you would rather sell your soul to Satan
也不会出售更多的鱼给天使湾，你懂了吗
then sell more fish for Angel Bouchard, do you understand?
-我懂了  -非常好
- I understand  - Very Good
现在
Now
我希望你能给我介绍一下附近的船长
Would you be so kind as to introduce me to some of your fellow captains
巴纳巴斯，你为什么要盯着卡洛琳的房间？
Barnabas, why are you staring into Caroline's room?
那是什么东西？
What is that thing?
-那是台灯  -看起来像血液
- Its a Lamp  - Look like blood
我认为是时候给你看下我的实验室了，巴纳巴斯
I think its time I show you my office, Barnabas
你知道精神科医生是什么吗？
You know what a psychiatrist is?
令人遗憾的是这个词本身对我很陌生
Regrettably the word is foreign to me
我也许可以猜测它是一些美国佳肴
may I assume it's some species of American delicacy
我是医学博士，专攻于心理的
Its a medical doctor that specializes in the mind
我是精神病专家
I'm a psychiatrist
现在
now
-你是哪里出生的？ -利物浦
- Where were you born?    - Liverpool
-你能描述一下那里吗？  -那里是肮脏的
- Can you describe it to me? - It's filthy
街上散发着泥土的味道
The street reeks smells of dirt
排泄物的味道充斥在空气中
smell of urine permits the air
你有催眠的经验吗？ 巴纳巴斯
Have you any experience with hypnosis Barnabas?
-我发现它很有用，对吗？ -没错，我同意
- I find it very useful, yes? - Yes, I agree
你想下
You see
有时候我们制造一个幻想世界
sometimes we make up a fantasy world
帮助我们消除过去可怕的记忆
to help us erase horrible memories of our pass
我发现催眠贯穿其中
I found Hypnotism cuts through all that
我发现它还可以用于其他目的
I found it for other purposes
我可以催眠你吗，巴纳巴斯？
May I hypnotize you, Barnabas?
夫人
Madam
我不相信会有一丁点的可能性
I do not believe  thatˇs remotely possible
好的
Good
现在
now
我想你告诉我一些事情
I like you to tell me a few things
一个吸血鬼
A vampire?
小声点
Keep your voice down
你究竟在说什么？
What on earth are you talking about?
哦，宽恕我，我只是催眠了他几个小时
Oh spare me, I had him under hypnosis for hours
巴纳巴斯？
Barnabas?
但他一直在帮我补全那些原本只是幻想的谬误
There is a point where all illusions fails but he's been bodge
他告诉我一切
He told me everything
奥克自从他回来时你所指的他的秘密
Including the fact that you known his secret since he arrived
你为什么一点也不说出来？
Why the hell didn't you say anything?
我想保护孩子
I was protecting the children
通过包藏一个吸血鬼？
By hiding a vampire in one of the guest bedroom?
你知道他已经承认在一个建筑工地杀了人
Do you know he admitted killing the men at a construction site,
他是凶手
he's a murderer
他是科林斯，一个好人
He's a Collins and a good man and
而且这些天来，这也只是一个巧合
these days, that's a desperately rare combination
哦，我差点忘了，科林斯家族是不会做错什么的
Oh yes, I almost forgot, the family that can do no wrong
你知道吗？茱莉娅，对你 我感到非常惊奇
You know Julia I'm surprised at you
我想作为你这一个专家，你会对他感兴趣的
I think a physician like you would find him fascinating
当然啊，在医学上，心理上
Well sure, medically, psychologically
肉体上他都是迷人的
physically he's fascinating
这就是为什么我来找你而不是警察
Which is exactly why I came to you instead of the police
如果他真的很迷人 朱莉娅
If fascinated Julia
如果你对这个家族还有一丁点爱和尊敬
if you have an atom love and respect for this family
就把你的嘴闭上
keep your mouth shut
与您讨论这个问题我感到不舒服
I'm don't feel comfortable discussing this with you
不用担心，我的孩子。我只是寻求一些建议
Do not fear my child，I simply seeking advice
这次只是关于女人方面的
only according  the woman of this time
有那个女人比你这个年纪更好呢？
and whom better choose than a woman of your age
你年纪多大了，如果可以告诉我的话
What is your age, if I may?
-15岁 - 15岁还没有丈夫？
- Fifteen - 15 and no husband?
你必须把那些胸部和臀部秀出来
You must put those bosom hips to use at once
除非你的女人气质消散或者已经凋零了
unless your womanhood will swollen up and die
你很奇怪
you're weird
你认为我奇怪是因为对于女人的态度太过生硬直接了吗
What do you think me too weird of a woman of this blunt
你显然是指维琪
You obviously mean Vicky
她是我看过的最丰满胸部和臀部的女人
She has the most fertile bosom hips I ever laid eyes upon
你太古怪了，你是这样想的么？
- You're way too weird      - Do you really think so?
你二逼，落伍，老套
You're stiff, proper, old fashion
维多利亚呢？
and Victoria?
她不是很正派吗？
Is she not proper?
其实她喜欢假装自己是摇滚乐手
She like to pretend she's rock and roll,
她肯定是卡朋乐队的粉丝
she's a carpenters fan chick for sure
你的意思是是说她当伐木工人时发生的一件事？
Are you mean saying she's has a thing for wood workers?
卡朋特就是音乐家，二逼
The Carpenters are musician stupid
哦 原来是音乐啊
Ah music
有时候我很喜欢音乐的
I am rather the fond of the music of the day
我是选择者，创始者
I am a picker I'm a beginner
我也是一个恋爱者
I'm a lover
同时我也是个罪人
and I am a sinner
在阳光下我玩我的音乐
I play my music in the sun
只有莎士比亚可以和我相提并论
Only a Shakespeare as I could
好的
Okay
如果你想和她在一起，你必须改变你的方法
If you want to get with her, you have to change your approach
把你那伦敦式甜蜜的怪异方式
Drop the whole weird sweet London thing
散播在普通的人群中去
hangout with a few normal people
你知道这场战争好的地方是什么吗？
Do you know what good about this war man?
赢得胜利？
to win?
现在听我讲 有什么好的地方关于这场战争 （越战）
No, listen up, what good about this war
如果这是最后一场战争的确不错
Is that its so bad its going to be the last war
- 是啊 - 的确
- Yeah  - Yeah
但是最后的战争
and this last war
什么时候到来？
When?
和平会来到的
Peace will made out
和平战胜所有的战争
Peace wins every war
- 每一场战争 -嗯
- Every war  -Yeah
你说的是和平
You speak of peace
我一直在棺木里度过将近2个世纪
I have spent the last two centuries locked in a box
只能盯着一片虚无
staring in the all consuming void
阴影反成了一种希望
the dark shadows of ones hopes
-哇，被锁了2个世纪？- 没错
- Wow, locked for 2 centuries? - Indeed
但是有个伟大的目标让我
But with great purpose let me thinks
坚信我会找到真爱
for I believe that I have found my one true love
矣，我却不知道如何才能取得她的温情
Alas I know not how to win her tender affection
我还担心我进不了她的视线里
but I fear that I have no willing in her eyes
- 他们说的就是我们  - 对
- That what they say about us  - Yeah
我算老几啊
Where I'm from
只要把钱给她的父亲就可以得到女孩的爱....或者是羊
the love of a woman is won by giving money to her father ... or sheep
如果让爱更加真诚
and if love is true enough
或许两样都要
perhaps the combination of the two
女人不会在意钱
women don't care about money
或者羊
or sheep
你确定？
Are you absolutely certain?
爱情，就像老鼠爱大米，先生
Love, chicks dig love, man
- 是的 - 嗯
- Yeah - Yeah
是的
Yes
我想起了埃里克西格尔精彩小说-爱的故事里面所写的
I remind of the line Eric Siegel wonderful novel, The Love Story
爱意味着永远不用说出口
Love means never having to say
对不起
you are sorry
然而请要记住要有真诚的后悔之意
however please know that is with sincere regret
现在我必须要杀死你们
that I must now kill all of you
啊
Yeah
不，真实杰出，尽管是在理论上
No, its brilliant, theoretically anyway
通过一系列的输血净化你的血
series of transfusion to try and purify your blood
但我的灵魂依然存在
and my soul exists
我应当警告你 巴纳巴斯 它会有很小的可能性会失效
I shall warn you Barnabas, there's a slight chance it wont work
正是因为这样，他们才会叫你待在医学院里学医
This is exactly the kind of thing they teach you in medical school
要有信心 医生
You must have faith doctor
当人可以成为一个怪物时
When as a man can become a monster
怪物也可以变成一个人
any monster can become a man
为什么你想要成为一个人，巴纳巴斯？
Why do you want to become a man, Barnabas?
你为什么要选择放弃永恒的青春？
Why do you chose to give up the gift of eternal youth?
看着我，每年我都要衰老
and look at me, every year I look half as pretty and twice as strong
这没错，夫人，但你现在已经是
That is true, Madam, you must have started as the most beautiful creature
在地球表面上最美的生物了
lived on the surface of the Earth
巴纳巴斯
Barnabas
你知道什么叫医生和病人的隐私吗？
Are you aware of the concept of doctor and patient confidentiality?
不知道
No
也许你会好心地开导我
Perhaps you would be kind enough to enlighten me
没问题
Alright
巴纳巴斯
Barnabas
维多利亚
Ah Victoria
你介意我跟着你吗？
Mind if I tag along?
没有比这更让人开心了
nothing would make me happier
你是来这里看海潮的吗？
Do you come for the stream?
事实上 我是下来找 戴维的
Actually I came down looking for David
天知道他跑哪去了
God knows where run off to now
如果能在圣诞节看到他，我们已经很幸运了
We will be lucky if we see him before Christmas
他是个不错的小伙子
He's a fine lad
我曾经也像他那样好奇和烦人
He but curious and annoying as I was
他非常崇拜你
he idolizes you
包括你和他母亲
Between you and his mother,
我和他谈不了其他任何东西
I can't get him to talk about anything else
你相信他，就是他可以看到她母亲并且和她讲话吗？
Do you believe him, that he see her and speak to her?
至少我相信他是一个在寻求安慰的寂寞男孩
Part of me believes that he's a lonely boy looking for comfort
我相信这世上有些事是我们不能理解的
part of me believes in things in this world we don't understand
例如魔法盒、死亡，还有命运
Things like magic and death, destiny
我一直在猜，如果能让他快乐，别人怎么认为也没什么大不了
I guess a long it makes him happy, it doesn't matter what anyone believe
完美的吐槽
Elegantly put
或者我们对于安琪太过于认真了
Maybe we're getting too work up about this Angie
我的意思是说他们只不过是装腔作势和翻修房子
I mean they spook up the canary and renovated the house,
那怎么样，我们仍然掌握着95%的份额了
so what? We still hold things on 95% of it
- 掌控着整个大浅滩-他说的没错
- grinding the Grand Banks- He's right
这并不意味着任何人都可以碰我们的底线
This doesn't mean anything to our bottom line
这并不意味着任何人？
doesn't mean anything?
这并不意味着任何人
Doesn't mean anything?
我的曾祖母创立天使湾就是为了如此
My great great grandmother started Angel Bay to show those
柯林斯家族，他们没有自己海域
Collins, they didn't own water
他们不会放低他们的身价来接近我们的
they couldn't look down their entitle nose at us
布沙尔已经掌控超过2个世纪的时间了
Bouchard woman enslaved for over 2 centuries
牺牲他们生命来捍卫现在的这个家业
Sacrificing their lives to build this business
这就意味着我们有一些事要做了。先生们
So that means something gentlemen
我绝不会让这家公司被那些柯林斯给击倒的
and I'll be damned if I let this company destroyed by those Collins
安排召开会议
call an arranged meeting
卖给你？绝不
Sell to you? Never
没有人能把金钱凌驾于家族荣誉至上
One cannot put a price on the restoration of the family honor
我会的
let me try
巴纳巴斯 柯林斯的支票
Check for Barnabas Collins
1 750 000
ONE MILLION SEVEN HUNDRED & FIFTY THOUSAND
我不知道我的商业头脑会让你这么害怕
I had no idea that my business acumen giving you such spasm
催眠渔民不是商业智慧 巴纳巴斯
hypnotizing fishermen isn't business acumen Barnabas
- 那是我的条件 - 这是我的条件
- Those are my terms - This are my term
去你的，下地狱让撒旦去吮吸
go is thou to hell and swiftly please Satan hedonist suckle
你那诅咒的乳房吧
of your disease tits
没有人像你这样对我讲话
Oh, no one talks like you anymore Barnabas
是的，的确
Yes, indeed
对于我，这个年纪仍然保持神秘色彩
I must say that this age does still remain a mystery to me
给我一个好的理由为什么不直接杀了你
Give me one good reason why shouldn't kill you this instant
- 因为我会杀了你如果你尝试这样做得话 -不可能
- If I'll kill you if you try- Impossible
那将需要仁慈心怀，而你没有
That would requires mercy
你反而将我变成了一个怪物 -我们都是怪物
- instead had made me a monster - We're both monsters, Barnabas
就像一山二虎
Just two big fish in a itty bitty pond
现在，二虎相争，必有一伤
Now, we can either fight until one of us is dead
或者
or
我们可以联盟
we can mate
那些弱小的势力
Little fish together
几个世纪以来我承认我对你感到非常愤怒同时
I'll be honest I was really angry at you for a century or so
不断地看着你的家族蠕动着
sure it was hmm watching your family squirm
消亡这就像是频临死亡的蚂蚁
and burn away like ants under magnifying glass
同时那也有趣的科学家族处处遇阻
and yes it was fun being adored as the Collins name hurdle
绝望的不断流失自己的财富
going wealthy on act of their despair
但是太迟了
but lately
太迟了以至于它还是发生了
Lately it just been
孤独
Lonely
我们与其他人是不同的，巴纳巴斯
We're different from this people Barnabas
我们比他们更强
We're better than they are
那就是
That's why
我怀念你的原因
I miss you
你是唯一我不能烧死的蚂蚁
You're the only ant I could not burn
你到底想要什么，安吉利？-你的爱
- What is it you want Angelique? - Your love
你还爱着我不是吗?
You do still love me don't you?
深藏在你冰冷的内心深处
Somewhere deep down in that cold beating heart
放手吧，即使是月老也不会成全我们这般可恶的组合
my dear even aphrodite herself cannot consult a more odious union
-那说明可以让我与你结盟？ -用什么？另一个诅咒？
- What if I mate you? - With what? A spell?
扮家家酒那并不是爱
Little dolls and pins that is not love
用这个
With this
这个你一度渴望的身体
The body you once begged me for
我必须承认，他们还在保质期
I must admit, they have not aged a day
我想要这一切结束，巴纳巴斯
I'm willing to start over Barnabas
我想要和你重归旧好
I'm willing to call a truce if just take me
我不再像以前那样冲动了 - 我能试着改变
- I am not as I once was - I could change that
那我如果拒绝呢？ -我会带走你索爱的所有人
- and if I refuse? - I take it with whom you loved
开始就是你所无比恋爱的小可怜
Starting with that little creature that you been eyeing so fondly
那个像是Jossete的姑娘
The one that looks like Jossete
好吧
Well then
我猜，现在无法抗拒了
I suppose, strictly unopposed now
我现在
I must now
要挑衅背负恶魔之名的女人了
Defiant the most enduring the women of Satan
这真是令人后悔的转变
That was regrettable turn of events
你不需要感到后悔 -是
- You didn't seem to regret it - Yes
看起来就算是已死之人对于活人来说我还是虚弱不堪
Seems that even in death,I have the weakness for a living flesh
尤其对于你来讲
especially yours
那是多么可惜用这样冷酷的方式来修辞如此有爱的事实
What a cold way to describe something so interesting
可能
perhaps
但我不会再屈服于你的魅力
but I cannot succumb to your charm ever again
请原谅我
Please, forgive me
如果我得不到你属于我的爱
if I can't have you my love,
那我将会毁了你
I'll destroy you
五分钟或更久
Five more minutes
这是非常幼稚的节目
this is a very silly play
是啊，这是我们唯一能到达的阶段
Yeah well its the only station we got around here
感觉怎么样？
How are we doing?
我还没感觉到我更像人类
I do not feel as I becoming more human yet
- 给我一点时间       - 时间
- Give it some time  - Time
关于时间我有很不幸的经历
I have unfortunate access of
我最喜欢露西火红色的头发
My favourite thing about Lucy is her crazy red hair
我的意思是盯着她的头发看
I mean look at her red hair
我第二喜欢的有关与她的
and my second favourite thing about her
就是她闪着光的粉色蝴蝶结
is her nice shiny pink bow
不要，求求你
No, please
我求求你
Please, I beg of you
妈妈，求求你
Mommy, please
妈妈。爸爸，救命
Mummy, daddy, help me
求求你们
Please
救我
help me
救救我
要我帮你什么？
help you what?
- 什么？ - 一个盛大的舞会
- A what? - A ball and a splendid one
- 一个舞会？邀请谁？ - 全城的居民
- A ball? For who? - The entire town of course
你不知道全镇的人都在恨我们吗？
Don't you know that the entire town kinda hate us?
宴会是权力和身份最好的证明
Ball are the illustration of power
宴会将会巩固我们家族的地位
Balls how ruling class remains ruling class
正是我一直说的，这个家族需要举办一些宴会
Exactly what I've been saying,this family could use some Balls
确实，柯林斯家族一直都有
Indeed and the Collins family have always
举行过规模最大以及最好的宴会
held the biggest and the most wonderful Balls
巴纳巴斯说得对
Barnabus has a point
是时候我们打开大门
its about time we open some door around
让那些乡下人明白我们已经回来了
Show the peasant that we're back in action
人们不再关注于愚蠢的舞会了
People don't throw balls anymore stupid
他们不关注？
They do not?
他们关注时下发生的一切
They throw happening
那他们怎么才会对我们的舞会感兴趣？
and how do they throw this happening?
好吧，首先最重要的是你需要一个旋转球灯
Well first thing first,you'll need a mirrored ball
- 无论那是什么，我们都会拥有的 - 河里会有很多镜子的
- Whatever that is, we should have it - The rivers has lots of mirrors
凯若琳
Caroline
我们会拥有很多的
We shall have lot of it
同时
and
爱丽丝 库伯乐队
Alice Cooper
我好像记得有爱丽丝 库伯 这样一个人
I seem to recall Alice Cooper from my youth
-她还在柯林港居住？ - 大概是吧 (才怪)
- Has she reside in Collins Port? - Not exactly
好吧，尽管如此她也是我们的客人
Well she should be our guest nonetheless
你好
Hello
谢谢你邀请我
Thank you for having us
晚上好，欢迎来到柯林堡
Good evening, welcome to Collins Wood
这将是一个好的开始
I got to handed to you, this is a happening
唯一令人遗憾的是爱丽丝库伯
the only thing missing is Alice Cooper
也许你需要进去交点朋友
Perhaps you should go in and make acquittance
在晚会的娱乐消遣的同时
of yourself with the evening entertainment
我所见过最丑的女人
Ugliest woman I've ever seen
戴维，那个管理礼服的女服务员呢？
Mater David where is the female coat attendant?
我爸爸正在里面跟她谈话
My dad talking to her inside
让我在外面守着
told me to keep my fucking out
我确定他会的，戴维你做了一件了不起的事
I'm sure he did David.You've done a marvelous job
我想让你和其他人去看爱丽丝 库伯的表演
I would like to watch Alice Cooper with the others
-我的爸爸说过让我...- 去看那个库伯女
- My father said.. - Go and watch The Cooper woman.
你是对的关于那个家伙
You're right about the stuff
无所谓，没有人比你更好了，小猫咪
nothing but best for you pussy cat
那个小孩是谁？
Who is the kid?
我不知道，我从没见过他
I have no idea, I never saw him before
来这儿
Come here
妈妈，爸爸去哪了？
Mummy, where's daddy?
他离开我们太久了
He's been gone for so long
他还会回家来吗？
Will he ever coming home?
你在外面做什么,亲爱的？
Whatever are you doing outside, my dear?
- 你会得重感冒的 - 我喜欢那个歌手 巴纳巴斯
- You'll catch a death of cold - I like him Barnabas
因为他歌里满是谎言
He lied
我一直压抑着情感因为我害怕当你听到时会离我而去
I have withheld my tender affection of fear for pity you ran hearing it
我也不再与其他灵魂谈及我的感受
and I am not spoken my feeling to another soul
你经常说起你是我来生的礼物
You always spoke as if you were my birthday gift
是的
Yes
我不知道为什么我感觉我可以
I don't know why but for some reason I feel like I can
告诉你我的一切
tell you anything
那种感觉好像我一直都认识你
and its like I known you forever
- 是的 - 可能我是
- Yes  - and if I was
被催眠了
hypnotic
也许，但是请稍等
Yes but wait no
我要向你保证我绝没有用诡计来骗取你的爱
I have use no such trickery to summon your heart I assure you
我不知道为什么，我一直感觉到什么东西一直指引我到这里
I do not know why it is, I just know that always something pulling me here
把我带向了柯林堡
Pulling me to Collins Port
带向了你
To you
哦，我亲爱的维多利亚，我有冒犯你吗？
Oh my dear Victoria Have I offended thy?
不，对不起，这仅仅是
No, sorry its just
我会回报我所爱的人的
People I love having always love me back
我的家庭送走了我
My own family sent me away
把我困在牢笼里，因为那更简单
trap me under a rock because it was easier
要比拥有一个于总不同
than having a daughter who is different
被咒诅的女儿
Who was cursed
诅咒我能看到其他孩子看不到的东西
Cursed because I saw things other little children didn't
对于一个孩子来讲，那是最孤独也是最痛苦的阶段
Its the most loneliest, the most painful years a child could know
现在，不要动，玛吉雅，你只会痛一分钟
Now hold still Maggy, this would only hurt for a minute
虽然是如此的痛苦艰难，我却永远不会丢失我的信仰
as hard as I were, I never lost my will
我需要重见天日
I need to feel the sun on my face again
我要逃出这个地方
I want to get out of here
我必须逃出这个地方
I got to get out of here
因此我出去寻找一个新的家庭
So I get out in search of a new home
一种新的生活原理以往的痛苦
a new life far away from that pain
即使做梦也难以想象我现在又多么的快乐
Even in my wildest dream, I never thought I feel as happy as I feel now
抛弃自己唯一的骨肉仅仅是因为她拥有某种天赋
to betray ones only kin where she possess a gift
不，维多利亚，那是不可原谅的
No, Victoria it is unforgivable
你的父母应该接受无尽的地狱般的折磨
your parents should deserve to boil in hell everlasting suffers
嘿，你没有被邀请
Hey you are not invited
在我余生，我想找一个属于我的地方
for the rest of my life I wanted a place where I belong
一个可以感受家的温暖
a place where I feel at home again
可以感受到爱的地方
feel loved again
我找到了这个地方，就是柯林堡
and I found this place here at collins Wood
就是这儿
and here
我们必须不断努力
We must intensify our efforts
我又想变成人类了
I want resume the need to be human again
- 我需要解释  -我的神
- I can explain it - My God
你不是用你的血来让我变成人类
You're not using your blood to make me human
你想用我的血来获得永生
You're using my blood to make yourself immortal
巴纳巴斯，那不公平，只有你才能有那种天赋
Barnabas, you have a gift it isn't fair to keep all to yourself
神圣的柯林家族授予你无比的信任
sacred Collins family took you in the bestow trust upon you
- 你却不留余地地背叛他们的信任 - 我很抱歉
- You em-bracingly betray their trust - I'm sorry
我不想渐渐衰老，我想要变回原来的美貌
I just don't what to grow old I want to be beautiful again
我想要永生，就像你一样
I want to life forever, like you
我恐怕那是不可能的了
I'm afraid that is out of the question
一个人大概拥有5升的血
A man contains some 5 quarter of blood
我能够吸干他少于7.5秒钟
which of course I can consume in mere 7.5 seconds
但对于你，亲
But you, my dear
我将会控制在5秒以内
I will drink it less than five seconds
请不要杀我。你是一个好人，你是一个绅士
Please don't kill me. You're a good man, you're a gentlemen
-求求你，求求你  - 女士
- Please, please  - Madam
我不好也不是绅士而且我也绝不会原谅背叛
I'm neither good nor gentle I do not forgive
我必须告诉你，威利
I should tell you Willy
如果你向别人走漏一点风声
if you ever speak a word of this to anyone
我会用一种不友好的手段杀掉你
I should have kill you in an unpleasant manner
不要担心，巴纳巴斯先生，我从来都不喜欢这个婊子
Do not worry Mr. B I never liked the bitch anyway
拜托，我知道你在这里
Come on, I know you're here
美丽工艺品，不是吗？
Beautiful workmanship isn't it?
我只是在找...
I'm just looking for the
这个?
this?
我恐怖那没什么值得去偷的
There nothing worth stealing I'm afraid
很可惜，伊丽莎白只用它来存放羽毛球的器具
Sadly, Elizabeth use it for badminton equipment
那正是我要找的
That what I was looking for
你要干什么？
What are you?
我打算做一些事情
I was about to do something
驱除那些削弱我存在的潜在因素
repellent that sickens me to my very core
我打算给你一个机会
I going to give you a choice
- 什么机会？ -你或者留在柯林堡
- What choice? - Either you remain in collins Wood
然后时时刻刻
and devote all your every waking
做一个好父亲
moment to be become an exemplary father
戴维一直想要的那种父亲
A father David so desperately wants and deserve
- 还有吗？ - 还有就是你滚！
- or?  - or you leave
带笔足够的钱，滚到除这以外的任何地方，去过自私的生活
with sufficient to live your life peeving selfish lives else where
当我们需要霍夫曼医生的时候，她究竟去哪里了
Where on earth is Dr. Hoffman when we needed her
的确
Indeed
巴纳巴斯，你身上着火了
Barnabas, you're on fire
我命令你给我解除诅咒
I demand that you release me from my curse
太迟了
You're late
- 这是什么？ - 你这些天都在喝的东西
- What is that? - The only thing you drink these days
哪里来的？
Where does it come from?
没人会知道的，我保证
No one you know I promise
我早料到你会再闯进来的
I knew it wouldn't be long before you barge in begging
求我给你解除诅咒
me to making you mortal again
现在那个霍夫曼医生不在了
Now that Doctor Hoffman isn't around
也就没人能给你输血
anymore to give you a your little transfusion
是的
Yes
这非常可惜
Yes, it was ashamed
她有事突然走了
she was caught away in so suddenly
有意思
Interesting
我可不知道有谁没事会跑海底去呆着
I do not any people who had business meeting at the bottom of the ocean
她是个骗子
It was a liar
她偷我的血
She was stealing my blood
我们也不是什么正人君子
Aren't we being hypocrites?
你应该相当熟悉你的血也少坑蒙拐骗来的
Lying and stealing blood are things you rather familiar with
是的
Yes
我杀了霍夫曼医生。工人
I Killed Dr Hoffman and the work men
还有那些很潮的小青年也是我杀的
and some very nice and shaping young people
不过
but know this
我每杀一个人
with each life I take
我的灵魂就消亡一部分
a piece of my soul dies
我杀人还不都是
I kill only because I'm compelled to
被你用巫术和诅咒逼的
compelled by your witchcraft, by your curse
你为什么要这么对我？
Why have you done this to me?
不好意思
Its ashamed
你是如此令我着迷
You know you been smart enough to love me
一切都会过去的
I would have let it go
你他妈的睁眼说瞎话
Speak plainly snake
我让你的小女友跳了回悬崖
I sent you little girlfriend off the cliff once before
是什么让你认为这事我还干的出来？
What makes you think I wont do it again?
我有一个个提案，巴纳巴斯
I'm gonna offer you a business proposal Barnabas
最后通牒哦
my final offer
我们一起占了这块地盘
Either you rule this pond of mine side by side
开个夫妻店
partners and lovers
或者
or
我再把你放回你的棺材里去
I put you back in a box
我和你想的正好相反
I already prepared my counter proposal
你的提案太不要脸了
It read thusly
你怎么老爱拿你那种老脸一遍遍往
You may strategically place your
我屁股上贴
wonderful pond upon my ass and kiss it repeatedly
沉睡的火焰啊，听我的召唤，回归你的所在
Sleeping flame I summon thy to your form return
把这黑夜烧得如白昼，烧啊烧啊
Make the night as bright as day and burn baby, burn
要让你永远在棺材里呆着可不是件容易的事
Come to realize that shutting you in a box for all eternity is hard
所以我只能这么办了
So here's the deal
我会把你喜欢的东西全毁掉
I'm going to destroy everything you love
这样你才会有更多时间来想起咱们z
and you're going to take some more time to think about us
几百年后见，亲爱的
see you in a couple of centuries, lover boy
别生气，巴纳巴斯
Do not dismay, Barnabas
我们能再逃出这个噩梦的
We can again escape this nightmare
说不定十几二十年就够了
perhaps a few decades or so
谁？我听见你了
Hello? I hear you
亲，不管你是谁，别怕
Oh sweet glory be, who ever you are fear not
我不会害你的
I will not harm you
这多少年了？几个世纪？
How many year is it? How many centuries have I?
多久了？
How long have it been?
20分钟
Its been twenty minutes
哦 是戴维，你怎么知道我被关了？
Yes Master David, how on earth did you know I was imprison?
我妈妈告诉我的，你可能以为我秀透了吧
My mother told me, you probably think I'm crazy
年轻人，我可没想那么多
Young man, I think nothing of the sort
巴纳巴斯叔叔
Uncle Barnabas
你怎么放条女的内裤在脸上？
Why do you ladies underwear on your face?
这事不能细说，你家人在哪？维多利亚在哪？
Never mind of the matter, where is you family? Where is Victoria
我没有看见，维琪
I hadn't seen Vicky,
但现在所有人都在镇上
but everybody else is in the town
- 我们的产房大火 -我们必须救他们，快过来帮我
- watching our canary burn - We must save them , help me
戴维
Master David
或许你该先把我的链子解开
Perhaps you should unchain me first
汉克，我们得在拐角那再加派一组人手
Hank we need another brigade out in the corner
尽快把人疏散
as quick as you can get this people out of here
大家全部站到警戒线之外
Alright everybody, stand behind the line please
我的天，伊丽莎白火大了
Oh boy Elizabeth going to be furious
- 谢里夫，我们聊聊  - 我没空闲聊
- Sheriff, we need to talk  - I ainˇt got time to chit chat
- 镇子还TMD烧着呢！ - 那你也没时间
- The damn town burning  - You don't have time for proof
看柯林斯家族窝藏杀人犯的证据？
that Collins family is harboring a murderer?
是的，霍夫曼医生和那帮工人都是我杀的
Yes, I killed, Dr Hoffman and the workmen
还有那群正玩的疯狂的小年轻人
and those really pleasant young people
我勒了个去
I'll be damn
想想整个城镇都以他们命名
To think the whole town name after
我打赌柯林斯肯定已经逃了
I be willing to bet that Barnabas has already skipped town
不过我打赌你能找到他
And I be willing to bet you'll find
更多无辜的受害者
the corpses of more of his innocent victims in there
柯林斯家族用谋杀者来重建家族生意
The Collins family has rebuild their business with murder
我们镇决不能容忍这样的事情发生
Well I say not in my town
那有一个柯林斯家族的人
there one of them now
他很可能像通过纵火来掩盖他老板的证据
He probably the one who started the fire to cover his boss's track
是时候跑路了
Time to go
威利，发生什么事了
Willie, what on earth happened?
大火，杀人犯，暴民，快跑啊
Fire, the murder angry mob, run
戴维，进屋去
David, go inside
利兹
Liz
抱歉，跟我们走一趟
I'm sorry, we going to have to take you in
你们都要去
all of you
比尔
Bill
柯林斯家族建了这个镇
The Collins family built this town
我们用我们自己的船和网建了这个镇
We built it with our boats and our net
你们就是这样回报我们付出的心血？
The sacrifices of our blood and this is how you repay us
你们窝藏杀人犯
You been harboring a murderer
逮捕他们
arrest them
我很乐意跟你们走
I shall go willingly
无论等待我的是怎样的处罚
whatever punishment awaits
借过
provided
- 没人能动我的家族  - 站那不许动
- no harm falls my family  - Hold it right there
借过
Provided
布沙尔跟我都要被抓起来
Miss Bouchard goes with me
因为她也是个怪物
because she is no less a monster than I
也许这才是最好的结局，如果
Perhaps it best if
我们俩都挂掉的话
We're both destroyed
柯林斯先生，我警告你，退后
Mr Collins, back off, I'm warning you
来啊，杀我啊，让他们看看你到底是个什么东西
Go on, slaughter me, show them what you are
不
No
我会让他们看看我们是什么东西
I shall show them what we are
那个男的对安吉做了什么？
What did that man done to Angie?
不是柯林斯，是安吉，她是女巫
It is not him, it her, she's the witch
不好意思
Excuse me
先过我这一关
You got to get through me first lady
都回家去吧，这没什么可看的
Alright go back to your homes now There's nothing to see here
你本来应该爱我的，柯林斯
You should've loved me, Barnabas
如果你还爱我，这些都不该发生的
none of this would've happen if you just you loved me
我本该灭了你，这一切就都不会发生
I should have destroy you, It wont be nothing but misery
- 我把心都给了你 -你根本就没有心
- I gave you my hear  - You have no heart
你就是个天煞孤星，你周围的女人都要死
You're the cursed, woman are done living by you
朱塞特 霍夫曼医生
Josette, Dr Hoffman
还有你心爱的维琪
and you beloved Vicky
我命令你解除她的诅咒
I command you to release her from your curse
命令我？ 你当我是白痴啊
Command?, you're making me sick
躲过了
Missed me
去死吧，你个丑八怪
You hideous serpent go to the gates of hell
从我的房间滚出去
Get out of my room
安吉丽科
Angelique
从我房间滚出去
Get out of my house
你的房间？
your house?
够了，这些小把戏
Enough trickery
- 我好仰慕你。- 表扬我么？
- I worshiped you  - Praised me
- 我好崇拜你 - 鄙视我么？
- Adore you  - Despise me
很好
Alright
如果这个房子是科林斯家族的鲜血铸就
if Collins blood builds this house then
那就用血洗礼这里的一切
let us bathe it
离我们远点
let us alone
凯若琳
Caroline
凯若琳，上帝啊
Caroline, my God
我就是个狼人怎么了，我们的事以后再谈
I'm a werewolf okay, lets not make a big deal out of it
狗咆
Woof
你对我女人做了什么？
What have you done to my daughter?
哈哈，利兹
Well, Liz
你要实现大科林斯的家族梦还需要加点料啊
Your perfect Collins family fantasy lack of substance
所以呢，当凯若琳还在摇篮里的时候，我派狼人咬了她一下
so I sent the werewolf to bit Caroline in the cradle
就像我把戴维变成孤儿是最好不过了
Just like I make David no better than a bastard
当我把他老妈送海底去
When I sent his mummy to the ocean floor
跟金枪鱼喝茶的时候
to have tea with the tuna
至于你吧，亲爱的
and as for you my love
我杀了你爸妈
I killed your mother and father
我诅咒你家族，巴纳巴斯
I cursed your family, Barnabas
谁让他们拆散我们
they kept us apart
他们不知道我们是一类人，我们是上天注定
They never understood we're the same, we were meant to be
离他远点
Leave him alone
我想我还是先杀了你吧，孤儿
I think I'll kill you first, Orphan
戴维 快走
David get out
- 你的对头是我 -你们所有人我都不会放过
- Your quarrel is with me -My quarrel is with all of you
我警告你，这是你最后一次机会
I'm warning you, this is your last chance
放了我们
and let us go
我不放你又能怎么样呢，你个野种
And what will you do if I don't you bastard
不是我想怎么样，是我妈
Not me, but my mom
走
Go
戴维 快走
David, come on
维利，快起来
Willie, come on
这就是故事的结局吗？
so this is how it ends?
如此安静
So quiet
你就像睡着了一样
as if you were asleep
你知道有段时间我爱过你
You know there was a time that I might have loved you
我们曾经也是可以永远在一起的
We could have spent eternity together
我们现在也可以啊
we still can
你要的不是爱
You never wanted my love
- 你要的只是占有我 - 不是的
- You wanted to posses me - No
我爱你，巴纳巴斯
I love you, Barnabas
你不可能去爱的，安吉利科
You cannot love, Angelique
那就是你的诅咒
That is your curse
本片由‘新气息论坛’‘001影视网’联合出品
最新电影首发，万部电影，电视剧下载
新气息论坛www.xinqixi.com 001影视网www.001ys.com
接受它吧
Take it
维多利亚，维多利亚
Victoria, Victoria
她朝那山去了
She set for that hill
我们现在怎么办？
What do we do now?
该怎么办
What we will always done
就怎么办
and do
我还以为失去你了
I thought I lost you
你已经失去我了
You have lost me
我生活在阳光底下，巴纳巴斯你生活在阴暗里
I live in the light Barnabas, you live in the shadow
我会老会死，你却永远不会
I'll grow old and die, you'll live forever
我们能找到解决办法的，亲爱的
We will find a way, my love
- 只有一种办法 - 不
- There's only one way - No
不能眼睁睁看着你跟我遭一样的罪，绝不
I will not see you suffer as I do, never
不
No
维多利亚，亲爱的维多利亚
Victoria, my sweet Victoria
维多利亚Victoria
朱塞特
Josette
古话说，血浓于水
It is said that blood is thicker than water
血在定义我们，约束我们
It is what defined us, binds us
也在诅咒我们
curses us
我的名字叫巴纳巴斯 柯林斯
My name is Barnabas Collins
我的诅咒最后被解除了
and my curse have finally been broken
本片由‘新气息论坛’‘001影视网’联合出品
最新电影首发，万部电影，电视剧下载
新气息论坛www.xinqixi.com 001影视网www.001ys.com